Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Organizations PE.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- O, 301676
  - Our Generation: Pamphlets and Publications III, 1964-1970, undated; 301672 (Box 76)
  - Our Generation: Pamphlets and Publications IV, 1964-1970, undated; 301673 (Box 76)
  - Our Generation: Pamphlets and Publications V, 1964-1970, undated; 301674 (Box 76)
  - Our Generation: Pamphlets and Publications VI, 1964-1970, undated; 301675 (Box 76)
  - Ouvriers Belges en Belgique (Belgium Workmen), 1916; 301677 (Box 76)
- P, 301694
  - Pacesetters, 1971-1977, undated; 301678 (Box 77)
  - Pacific Coast Labor School (Berkeley, CA), 1941; 301679 (Box 77)
  - Pacific News Service (Japanese farmers), undated; 301680 (Box 77)
  - Pacific Northwest Labor History Association (Seattle, WA), 1995-; 301681 (Box 77)
  - Pacific Northwest Research Center (Eugene, OR), 1974-; 301682 (Box 77)
  - Pacific Publishing Foundation, undated; 373047 (Box 77)
  - Pacific Rim Coalition, undated; 373861 (Box 77)
  - Pacific Street Films (Brooklyn, NY), 1981; 301683 (Box 77)
  - Pacific Studies Center, 1970; 301684 (Box 77)
  - Pacifica Radio, circa 1970, undated; 301685 (Box 77)
  - Pacifica Radio Archive, 1980-; 301686 (Box 77)
  - Painters Free Press, 1966; 301687 (Box 77)
  - Palestine Activist Forum (New York), undated; 301688 (Box 77)
  - Palestine Human Rights Campaign, 1981-; 301689 (Box 77)
  - Palestine Solidarity Committee, 1976-, undated; 301690 (Box 77)
  - Pamphlet Press, 1945; 375406 (Box 77)
  - Pan Africanist Congress of Anzania, 1977-1979; 301691 (Box 77)
  - Pan-Pacific Trade Union Conference (Hankow, China), 1927; 301692 (Box 77)
  - Panorama DDR, 1985; 375407 (Box 77)
  - Paper Tiger Television, 2007-; 301693 (Box 77)
  - Paris American Committee for July 4 Demonstration, undated; 374358 (Box 77)
  - Park Slope Greens (New York), 2002; 301695 (Box 77)
  - Partai Sosialis Indonesia: Pamphlet, 1956; 301696 (Box 77)
  - Parti Communiste de Belgique, 1936; 301697 (Box 77)
  - Parti Communiste Francais, 1937; 301698 (Box 77)
  - Parti Communiste Francais: Opposition Leniniste, 1927; 301699 (Box 77)
  - Parti Communiste Internationaliste, 1961; 301700 (Box 77)
  - Parti Democratique de Guinee, 1959; 301701 (Box 77)
  - Parti Socialiste Belge, 1909-; 301702 (Box 77)
  - Parti Socialiste (France), undated; 301703 (Box 77)
  - Parti Socialiste SFIO (France) I, 1938-; 301704 (Box 77)
  - Parti Socialiste SFIO (France) II, 1938-; 301705 (Box 77)
  - Parti Socialiste SFIO (France) III, 1938-; 301706 (Box 77)
  - Parti Socialiste Unifie (France), 1968; 301707 (Box 77)
  - Parti Unifie des Communistes Haitiens, 1981; 301708 (Box 77)
  - Partido Comunista de Colombia: Comite Central, undated; 301709 (Box 77)
  - Partido Comunista do Brazil, 1946-1964; 301710 (Box 77)
  - Partido Comunista de Venezuela, 1946; 437196 (Box 77)
  - Partido Mexicano Socialista, circa 1921; 301711 (Box 77)
  - Partido Revolucionario Institucional, 1949; 301712 (Box 77)
  - Partido Socialista Argentino, 1925; 301715 (Box 77)
  - Partido Socialista Democratico (Argentina), 1962; 301716 (Box 77)
  - Partido Socialista Puertorriqueno, 1975-; 301717 (Box 77)
  - Partido Vanguardia Revolucionaria (Peru), 1978; 301718 (Box 77)
  - Partij Van de Arbeid, 1948; 301719 (Box 77)
  - Partisan Defense Committee, 1976-; 325117 (Box 77)
  - Partisan Party, 1971; 301720 (Box 77)
  - Partisan Defense Committee, 1976-; 301721 (Box 77)
  - Partito Comunista Italiano, 1979; 301713 (Box 77)
  - Partito Comunista Unificato D'Italia, undated; 301714 (Box 77)
  - Partizdat Tsk VKP, 1932-; 301723 (Box 77)
  - Party for Socialism and Liberation, 2004, undated; 373048 (Box 77)
  - Party for Workers Power, 1974; 301724 (Box 77)
  - Party of Labour of Albania, 1961-1966; 380106 (Box 77)
  - Pastors for Peace, 1993-, undated; 301725 (Box 77)
  - Patriot Party, 1970; 301726 (Box 77)
  - Patriotic Research Bureau in Defense of Christianity and Americanism, 1941; 301727 (Box 77)
  - Paul Robeson International Settlement (Detroit, MI), 1983-; 301728 (Box 77)
  - Pax Christi (NYU), undated; 301729 (Box 77)
  - Peace Action, 2009-; 351050 (Box 78)
  - Peace Action Center (Washington, DC), 1962-; 301730 (Box 78)
  - Peace Action Committee (Nutley, NJ), 1972; 325118 (Box 78)
  - Peace Action Council of Southern California, 1971; 325119 (Box 78)
  - Peace Action Education Fund, undated; 325120 (Box 78)
  - Peace Action New York State, undated; 373049 (Box 78)
  - Peace Activities Coordinating Council (PACC) (Los Angeles, CA), undated; 301731 (Box 78)
  - Peace and Freedom Association, 1969; 301732 (Box 78)
  - Peace Association of Friends in America, 1915; 301766 (Box 78)
  - Peace Corps, 1962; 328013 (Box 78)
  - Peace Council of the German Democratic Republic, 1969-1971; 301767 (Box 78)
  - Peace Development Fund, 1995-; 351036 (Box 78)
  - Peace House (New York, NY), 1925; 301768 (Box 78)
  - Peace Information Center, 1950-; 325121 (Box 78)
  - Peace Literature Service, 1960; 437194 (Box 78)
  - Peace Museum (Chicago, IL), undated; 301769 (Box 78)
  - Peace News Ltd: Pamphlets, 1946-1954; 301770 (Box 78)
  - Peace Patriots, circa 1932; 301771 (Box 78)
  - Peace Pledge Union: Activist Group, undated; 301772 (Box 78)
  - Peace Publications Committee, 1964; 301773 (Box 78)
  - Peace Publications (pamphlet: Government Sponsorship of the Arts), 1961; 301774 (Box 78)
  - Peace Through Change That Begins With Me, undated; 374766 (Box 78)
  - Peace Treaty Campaign, 1988; 374765 (Box 78)
  - Peacemakers (New York, NY), undated; 301775 (Box 78)
  - PeacePAC, 1982; 301776 (Box 78)
  - Peacesmith, Inc., undated; 301777 (Box 78)
  - Peking Review (pamphlets), 1973; 301778 (Box 78)
  - Penicillin For Vietnam, undated; 373050 (Box 78)
  - Pennsylvania Child Labor Association, 1907, 1928; 301779 (Box 78)
  - Pennsylvania Civil Liberties Committee, 1932; 328025 (Box 78)
  - Pennsylvania Committee for Total Disarmament, 1924-1935; 301780 (Box 78)
  - Pennsylvania Committee to Defend the Pittsburgh Six, undated; 335717 (Box 78)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Voluntary Relief Department, 1952; 301781 (Box 78)
  - Pennsylvania Woman Suffrage Association, 1915; 301782 (Box 78)
  - Penny Phone League (Chicago, IL), undated; 301783 (Box 78)
  - Pentagon Papers Fund, 1970s; 301784 (Box 78)
  - Pentagon Papers Peace Project, undated; 301785 (Box 78)
  - People Against Racism, 9164, undated; 301786 (Box 78)
  - People Before Profits, undated; 373051 (Box 78)
  - People for Peace, 1971; 374129 (Box 78)
  - People for Peace (Columbia University, New York, NY) (national student anti-war conference), 2002; 305497 (Box 78)
  - People to Abolish Abortion Laws, circa 1969; 301787 (Box 78)
  - People United for Affirmative Action (PUFAA), undated; 301788 (Box 78)
  - People United for Justice, 1979; 301789 (Box 78)
  - People v Ashcroft, undated; 347843 (Box 78)
  - Peoples' Alliance, 1979-1980; 301790 (Box 78)
  - People's Anti-War Mobilization, 1981-1987; 301791 (Box 78)
  - People's Bicentennial Commission I, 1973-; 301792 (Box 78)
  - People's Bicentennial Commission II, 1973-; 301793 (Box 78)
  - People's Campaign-Justice @ Wal-Mart, 2002; 301794 (Box 78)
  - People's Coalition for Peace and Justice I, 1971-1973; 301795 (Box 78)
  - People's Coalition for Peace and Justice II, 1971-1973, undated; 301796 (Box 78)
  - People's Coffee Grounds (New York, NY), 1970-; 301797 (Box 78)
  - People's Coffee House (New York, NY), undated; 301798 (Box 78)
  - People's College (Fort Scott, KS), undated; 301799 (Box 78)
  - People's Committee, 1942; 301800 (Box 78)
  - People's Committee Against Hearst (Washington, DC), undated; 301801 (Box 78)
  - Peoples Committee Against Pogroms in Poland, circa 1936; 304561 (Box 78)
  - Peoples' Congress of Apllied Religion, undated; 335872 (Box 78)
  - People's Convention (London), 1941; 301802 (Box 78)
  - People's Cooperating Communities Trucking Collective, 1975; 373052 (Box 78)
  - People's Co-operative State Bank (Hammond, IN), 1923, undated; 301803 (Box 78)
  - People's Council of America for Democracy and Peace, 1917, undated; 301804 (Box 78)
  - People's Court Comrades, 1975-1976; 301805 (Box 78)
  - People's Culture Union of America, 1948; 301806 (Box 78)
  - People's Drama, 1934; 301807 (Box 78)
  - People's Educational Center (Hollywood, CA), 1944-1946; 301808 (Box 78)
  - People's Fund, the, 1980; 301809 (Box 78)
  - People's History Museum (Great Britain), 2002-; 301810 (Box 78)
  - Peoples' House, 1918; 336116 (Box 78)
  - People's Information Center/ New York Switchboard, undated; 325122 (Box 78)
  - People's Information Relay, 1978; 301811 (Box 78)
  - People's Institute, circa 1914, undated; 325123 (Box 78)
  - People's Institute of Applied Religion, 1944-; 301812 (Box 78)
  - People's Law School (San Francisco, CA), 1974; 301813 (Box 78)
  - People's Lawsuit to Set Aside the 1972 Elections, 433915 (Box 78)
  - People's League, undated; 301814 (Box 78)
  - People's Legislative Service, 1924-1925; 301815 (Box 78)
  - People's Life Fund, 1971; 374089 (Box 78)
  - People's Lobby I, 1930-1949; 301816 (Box 78)
  - People's Lobby II, 1930-1949; 301817 (Box 78)
  - People's May Day Committee, undated; 334601 (Box 78)
  - People's Museum (Woodside, NY), circa 1970s; 325124 (Box 78)
  - People's Party (Milwaukee, WI), 1973; 373053 (Box 78)
  - People's Party (New York, NY), 1936-1937; 301818 (Box 78)
  - People's Party (Washington, DC), 1971-1974; 301819 (Box 78)
  - People's Party of the United States of America, 1947; 301820 (Box 78)
  - People's Peace Treaty, 1971, undated; 301822 (Box 79)
  - People's Platform Conference (New York, NY), 1970; 301823 (Box 79)
  - People's Power League, 1920; 301824 (Box 79)
  - People's Press (Minneapolis, MN), 1916; 328480 (Box 79)
  - People's Press I, 1969-; 301825 (Box 79)
  - People's Press II, 1969-; 301826 (Box 79)
  - People's Print, undated; 301827 (Box 79)
  - People's Progress Slate, 1965; 373918 (Box 79)
  - People's Progressive Party (Guyana), 1971, undated; 301828 (Box 79)
  - People's Publishing House Ltd Bombay, 1953; 437193 (Box 79)
  - People's Reconstruction League, undated; 301829 (Box 79)
  - People's Russian Information Bureau (London), 1919; 301830 (Box 79)
  - People's School for Marxist Studies (New York, NY), 1983-; 301831 (Box 79)
  - People's Songs, Inc. (Pete Seeger), undated; 301832 (Box 79)
  - Pere Lachaise Cemetery (Paris, France), undated; 301833 (Box 79)
  - Permanent International Committee for Recognition of the GDR, 1971; 380108 (Box 79)
  - Permanent Revolution Group, 1987-1988; 328027 (Box 79)
  - Peter Miller Films, Inc., 2001; 301834 (Box 79)
  - Peter V. Cacchione Association, undated; 437191 (Box 79)
  - Petrograd Council of Workers' and Soldiers' Deputies, 1917; 301835 (Box 79)
  - Peuple, 1932; 301836 (Box 79)
  - Phelps-Dodge Workers Defense Committee, undated; 325125 (Box 79)
  - Phelps-Stokes Fund: Emergency Committee for African Refugees, 1982; 301837 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Free Press, 1971; 301845 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Gay Liberation Front, 1970; 301838 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Marxist School, 1990; 301839 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Reproductive Rights Coalition, undated; 380110 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia School of Social Science and Art, undated; 301840 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Solidarity, 1973-; 301841 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Tageblatt, 1936; 301842 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Women's Trade Union League, 1921; 301843 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Workers' Organizing Committee, 1977, undated; 301844 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Workers School, 1939; 325126 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Yearly Meeting of the Religious Society of Friends: Civil Liberties Committee, 1954; 301846 (Box 79)
  - Philippine Resource Center (Berkeley, CA), 1980s; 301847 (Box 79)
  - Philippine Workers Support Committee, undated; 301848 (Box 79)
  - Phoenix Anarchist Coalition (Ann Arbor, MI), 1969; 301849 (Box 79)
  - Physicians for a National Health Program, 2010-; 325127 (Box 79)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility, 1967; 301850 (Box 79)
  - Picture the Homeless (New York, NY), 2010, undated; 301851 (Box 79)
  - Piedmont Rural Research Cooperative, 1966; 373921 (Box 79)
  - Pierre Degeyter Club (New York, NY), 1935; 301852 (Box 79)
  - Pig International Party, 1968; 301853 (Box 79)
  - Piney Woods School, 1950-; 325128 (Box 79)
  - Pink Sheet on the Left (Washington, DC), 1980; 301854 (Box 79)
  - Pioneer Aid and Support Association, 1927; 301855 (Box 79)
  - Pioneer Book Service (London), 1968; 301856 (Box 79)
  - Pioneer Women I, 1929-; 325129 (Box 79)
  - Pioneer Women II, 1929-; 325130 (Box 79)
  - Pioneer Youth of America, 1925-1948; 301857 (Box 79)
  - Pioneers for Women's Rights, undated; 380112 (Box 79)
  - Pittsburgh Civil Rights Congress, 1952-1955; 301858 (Box 79)
  - Pittsburgh Marxist Study Group, undated; 373054 (Box 79)
  - Pittsburgh Socialist Education League, undated; 301859 (Box 79)
  - Plain Talk (pamphlets; published by Catholic Information Society), 1947, undated; 301861 (Box 79)
  - Planetary Citizens, 1972; 301860 (Box 79)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1970-; 325131 (Box 79)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population, 1970-1974; 373055 (Box 79)
  - Planning Council of America (housing), undated; 325132 (Box 79)
  - Play School Conference, undated; 301862 (Box 79)
  - Plebs League (Great Britain), 1909-1949; 301863 (Box 79)
  - Ploughshares: Returned Peace Corps Volunteers Working for Peace (Seattle, WA), 1984; 325133 (Box 79)
  - Plumb Plan League (Washington, DC) (railroads), undated; 301864 (Box 79)
  - Pluto Press I, 1971-; 301865 (Box 79)
  - Pluto Press II, 1971-; 301866 (Box 79)
  - Pluto Press III, 1971-; 344710 (Box 79)
  - PM Press, 2008-; 301867 (Box 79)
  - Poale-Zion/ Zeire Zion, 1933, undated; 301868 (Box 79)
  - Point Blank (Berkeley, CA), 1972-1973; 301869 (Box 79)
  - Point of Production (Marxist journal), 1976-; 301870 (Box 79)
  - Polemic Publishers, 1934-1935; 334777 (Box 80)
  - Policy Alternatives for the Caribbean and Central America (PACCA), 1987, undated; 380114 (Box 80)
  - Polish-American Labor Council (Chicago, IL), 1945; 301871 (Box 80)
  - Polish-American Trade Union Committee, 1941; 346529 (Box 80)
  - Polish Committee of the Defenders of Peace (Warsaw, Poland), undated; 304352 (Box 80)
  - Polish Information Center, 1944, undated; 301872 (Box 80)
  - Polish Labor Group (New York, NY), 1943-1944; 301873 (Box 80)
  - Polish Labor Underground Press, undated; 301874 (Box 80)
  - Polish Socialist Alliance, 1946; 328028 (Box 80)
  - Polish Socialist Party (Polska Partia Socjalistyczna): Delegation for Abroad, 1945-1947; 301875 (Box 80)
  - Polish United Workers Party (Poslka Zjednoczona Partia Robotnicza), 1950; 301876 (Box 80)
  - Political Action for Peace (Cambridge, MA), undated; 373056 (Box 80)
  - Political Education and Action Collective (New York, NY), undated; 301877 (Box 80)
  - Political Education Project (Boston, MA), 1973-1974; 301878 (Box 80)
  - Political Prisoners Defense and Relief Committee (New York, NY), 1919; 301879 (Box 80)
  - Political Prisoners Relief Committee (New York, NY), 1954; 301880 (Box 80)
  - Political Rights Defense Fund (New York, NY) I, 1976-1987, undated; 301881 (Box 80)
  - Political Rights Defense Fund (New York, NY) II, 1976-1987, undated; 301882 (Box 80)
  - Political Science Pocket Library (New York, NY) (pamphlet), 1931; 301883 (Box 80)
  - Political Victims' Welfare Committee, undated; 301884 (Box 80)
  - Politics Club (University of Chicago, IL), 1950-; 301885 (Box 80)
  - Poor People's Campaign, 1968; 325134 (Box 80)
  - Poor People's Corporation (Jackson, MS), circa 1970s; 301886 (Box 80)
  - Porcupine Freedom Festival, 2011; 423055 (Box 80)
  - Porcupine Press: Catalog, 1995; 301887 (Box 80)
  - Post War World Council (New York, NY), 1942-1964; 301888 (Box 80)
  - Post War World Council (New York, NY): Pamphlets I, 1942-1963; 301889 (Box 80)
  - Post War World Council (New York, NY): Pamphlets II, 1942-1963; 301890 (Box 80)
  - Potemkin Bookshop (booklet), undated; 342452 (Box 80)
  - Potomac Cooperative Federation (Washington, DC), 1948; 301891 (Box 80)
  - Pour Une Intervention Communiste (Paris), undated; 301892 (Box 80)
  - Pouren Defense Conference (New York, NY), 1909; 301893 (Box 80)
  - Poverty/ Rights Action Center (Washington, DC), 1966; 301894 (Box 80)
  - Prairie Fire Organizing Committee, 1970s; 301895 (Box 80)
  - Prairie School for Social Advance (Winnipeg, Canada), 1930-1945; 301938 (Box 80)
  - Praja Socialist Party (New Delhi, India), 1955, undated; 301939 (Box 80)
  - Press Association of Jamaica, undated; 373057 (Box 80)
  - Prime Time, 1972; 380115 (Box 80)
  - Princeton Area Sanctuary Committee, 1986-1987; 380116 (Box 80)
  - Princeton University: Industrial Relations Section (New Jersey) I, 1929-1957; 301940 (Box 80)
  - Princeton University: Industrial Relations Section (New Jersey) II, 1929-1957; 301941 (Box 80)
  - Prison Activist Resource Center (Berkeley, CA), 1999-; 301942 (Box 80)
  - Prison Comfort Club (Chicago, IL), 1918; 301943 (Box 80)
  - Prison Moratorium Project, circa 1996-; 301944 (Box 80)
  - Prisoners' Information and Support Service (Boston, MA), 1969; 301945 (Box 80)
  - Prisoners' Relief Committee, undated; 325135 (Box 80)
  - Prisoner's Rights Union, 1994; 325136 (Box 80)
  - Prisoners' Strike for Peace, undated; 301946 (Box 80)
  - Prisoners Solidarity Committee (New York, NY), 1972-; 301947 (Box 80)
  - Prisoners Solidarity Committee: Pamphlets (New York, NY), 1972-; 301948 (Box 80)
  - Prisoners Union (California), 1971-1975; 301949 (Box 80)
  - Private Health Insurance Must Go! Campaign, undated; 373058 (Box 80)
  - Privatization of Culture Project (NYU), 2000; 301950 (Box 80)
  - Probe Magazine's Communications Workshop, undated; 301951 (Box 80)
  - Pro-Democracy Campaign, undated; 301952 (Box 80)
  - Program of the National Liberation Front of South Vietnam, undated; 373709 (Box 80)
  - Progress Books (Toronto), 1964-1986; 373059 (Box 80)
  - Progress Publishers: Pamphlets, 1920, 1966-1975; 328029 (Box 80)
  - Progress Theatre, 2002; 301953 (Box 80)
  - Progressive Alliance (Washington, DC), 1979; 301954 (Box 80)
  - Progressive Books and Periodicals, 1969; 325137 (Box 80)
  - Progressive Bookshop (Long Island, NY), 1946; 328157 (Box 80)
  - Progressive Citizens of America (New York, NY), 1946-1947; 301955 (Box 80)
  - Progressive Coalition (New York, NY), undated; 325146 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Democrats of America, 2008-, undated; 301956 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Education Association (New York, NY), 1941-1942; 301957 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Forum (New York, NY), 1938, undated; 301958 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Movement (Brooklyn, NY), 1965; 301959 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Party, 1960-1969; 301960 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Party I, 1970-1979; 301961 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Party II, 1970-1979; 301962 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Party, 1980-; 301963 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Party I, undated; 301964 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Party II, undated; 301965 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Party: Pamphlets I, 1960-1969; 301966 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Party: Pamphlets II, 1960-1969; 301967 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Party: Pamphlets I, 1970-1979; 301968 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Party: Pamphlets II, 1970-1979; 301969 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Party: Pamphlets, 1980-; 301970 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Party: Pamphlets I, undated; 301971 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Party: Pamphlets II, undated; 301972 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor Party: Pamphlets III, undated; 301973 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Labor School (Boston, MA), 1936-1940; 301974 (Box 81)
  - Progressive League for Alfred E. Smith (New York, NY), 1928; 301975 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Librarians Guild, 1989-; 301976 (Box 81)
  - Progressive National Committee (New York, NY), 1913-1936; 301977 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party, 1912; 301978 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party, 1924; 301979 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party I, 1948; 301980 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party II, 1948; 301981 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party, 1949; 301982 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party, 1950; 301983 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party, 1951-1954; 301984 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party (Henry Wallace campaign), undated; 325147 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party: California, 1939; 301985 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party: Idaho, undated; 301986 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party: Illinois, 1947-1950, undated; 301987 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party: Oregon, 1939; 301988 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party: Pennsylvania, 1923, 1950; 301989 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party: Research Department (election campaign handbook), 1948; 377470 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Party: Western Pennsylvania, 1952, undated; 301990 (Box 81)
  - Progressive People's Publishers (New York, NY) (pamphlet), 1936; 335506 (Box 81)
  - Progressive Woman (Girard, KS), circa 1910; 301991 (Box 82)
  - Progressive Workers Movement, 1965; 301992 (Box 82)
  - Progressive Youth Organizing Committee, 1963-, undated; 301993 (Box 82)
  - Prohibition Party (Massachusetts), 1895; 301995 (Box 82)
  - Prohibition Party (New Jersey), 1895; 301994 (Box 82)
  - Project Achilles' Heel, undated; 380124 (Box 82)
  - Project Air War (Vietnam), 1972; 301996 (Box 82)
  - Project for a Women's Bill of Rights, 1975; 301997 (Box 82)
  - Project Pursestrings, 1970; 374339 (Box 82)
  - Project South, 2000-2001, undated; 373060 (Box 82)
  - Project Superwoman (domestic violence), undated; 325148 (Box 82)
  - Projects Collective, 2003; 325149 (Box 82)
  - Proletarian Party, 1937; 301998 (Box 82)
  - Proletarian Publishers, undated; 328162 (Box 82)
  - Proletarian Revolutionary Party, undated; 374353 (Box 82)
  - Proletarian School, 1918; 328163 (Box 82)
  - Proletarian Unity League, 1942-1980; 301999 (Box 82)
  - Proletarian Warriors, undated; 325150 (Box 82)
  - Prolibertad, 1998-; 302000 (Box 82)
  - Prolibertad Freedom Campaign, 2008; 373061 (Box 82)
  - Prolifers for Survival, 1980-; 302001 (Box 82)
  - Promoting Enduring Peace, Inc. I, 1954-; 302002 (Box 82)
  - Promoting Enduring Peace, Inc. II, 1954-; 302003 (Box 82)
  - Promoting Enduring Peace, Inc. III, 1954-; 302004 (Box 82)
  - Proportional Representation Campaign Committee, undated; 328181 (Box 82)
  - Prospect Lefferts Voices for Peace and Justice, undated; 302005 (Box 82)
  - Prostitutes of New York (PONY), undated; 302006 (Box 82)
  - Prout, 2010; 325151 (Box 82)
  - Provisional Committee for a Referendum on the Five-Cent Fare, 1948; 302007 (Box 82)
  - Provisional Committee for Cuba, undated; 302008 (Box 82)
  - Provisional Committee for the Defense of Trade Union Democracy, undated; 302009 (Box 82)
  - Provisional Committee to Aid Victims of Taft-Hartley, 437217 (Box 82)
  - Provisional Labor Committee for Workers' Rights in Spain, 1938; 302010 (Box 82)
  - Provisional Graphic Arts Committee for Peace, 1967; 374739 (Box 82)
  - Provisional Ohio Labor For Peace Committee, undated; 373700 (Box 82)
  - Provisional Organizing Committee for a Marxist-Leninist Party, 1958-1959; 302011 (Box 82)
  - Provisional Organizing Committee to Reconstitute the Marxist-Leninist Communist Party, USA, undated; 325152 (Box 82)
  - Provisional Trade Union Committee for Repeal of the Smith Act, 1951; 302012 (Box 82)
  - PSOE (Spanish Socialist Labor Party), 1900-1938, undated; 302013 (Box 82)
  - Psychologists for a Democratic Party, undated; 302014 (Box 82)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1936-1947; 302015 (Box 82)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1948-1949; 302016 (Box 82)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1951-1952; 302017 (Box 82)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1958; 302018 (Box 82)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1962-1963; 302019 (Box 82)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1964; 302020 (Box 82)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1965; 302021 (Box 82)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1966; 302022 (Box 82)